
SUPPORT STORE OWNERS!! STOP Plain Packaging!!

"Plain Packaging" : Dangerous, Expensive, Ineffective!!

The Government plans to impose "Plain Packaging" tobacco rules on retailers

It is DANGEROUS!!! You MAY Have Your Back Turned to Potential Robbers

It is EXPEN$$$IVE $$$$!! 7% wait time increase, costing your store a lot!!

It FAILED!!!Smoking Has Gone Up by 3.4%

SUPPORT STORE OWNERS!! STOP Plain Packaging!!
